(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2 Extra Episode=
The next challenge is called
Rapid Boarding Dash.
You'll need to board the same car
and close the doors within 30 seconds.
Then get out, board another car,
and close its doors.
Then open the doors and get out.
There's a time limit, right?
Yes.
How long?
30 seconds.
30 seconds?
Five cars?
No.
Two.
No problem then.
Our test run was 35 seconds.
You can do it.
Let's do it.
(Piece of cake)
Come on.
Okay.
Now, everyone head over
to the parking lot
and complete the challenge.
Let's go.
These two cars, right?
Let's think of a strategy first.
(Car 1)
(Car 2)
(Can't reach the back seat
of Car 1 directly)
We still need to move the seat.
Because squeezing into the back is slow.
It's actually fine.
Because the only requirement
is getting into the car.
We don't need to sit down.
We just need to get inside.
We'll just cram ourselves in.
You're pretty smart, aren't you?
We just need to figure out
our positions.
(Earth Group's big brains join forces)
So the driver and Yuwen
bolt straight to the passenger seat.
Yeah. Then the rest of us in the back
can figure it out any way we can.
No. They didn't say
there have to be six people in the back.
We could have four in the front.
You know what I mean?
Two people have to sit here.
I know.
If he doesn't sit on someone's lap,
how will you close the door?
You have to close it anyway.
And it's tough for two people
to sit here.
Two sit here.
Yeah.
No.
This is manageable.
Actually, what I suggest is...
Look.
(Just try it)
You just sit here.
That works.
Then three people max in the front.
(Experience is the best teacher)
Because that
is the driver's seat.
Driver's seat.
Yes, that won't work for the driver.
Three people then.
So the back is reduced to five.
Five?
Five is easy.
(Arrangement: 3 in front, 5 in back)
I put the bell in my pocket.
No. It won't ring.
It's fine.
No worries, Honglei.
You can always ring the bell for us.
Here's the thing, Yuning.
Let me finalize this.
We'll lock in the three in front.
Honglei, driver's seat.
You get out and run fast.
You go inside first.
Once we're there, you dive in first.
Then Yuwen gets in right after.
We just tested the front.
Three people can fit.
Okay?
Yes, okay.
The rest of us
can just use the back door.
Let's try and see if this row
can hold the five of us.
You mean five in this row?
Yeah.
(Five people on two seats)
Yeah, all we need is to close the door.
Experience is the best teacher.
Come on. Get in and see.
Number one.
Get in?
One.
(Quickly adjusting the position)
Fei, get in.
Fei is the second.
Okay.
I'll get in.
Three.
Maybe we can all sit in this row.
It works.
Come on. Hurry.
(Successfully squeezed in)
It works.
Wait.
Wang Yuwen's not in.
What about Wang Yuwen?
She's in the front.
What did we just say, Naiwen?
Isn't it that side?
It's the same.
The same.
Two in the passenger seat,
and one in the driver's.
It's always the two of us, Naiwen.
Wait.
How do I do this?
I come over here?
Yes.
Naiwen, just put your feet underneath.
That works?
Yeah, you're fine.
Okay.
Nice.
(Perfectly seated)
Wait. We still need to ring the bell.
Okay, get out.
Come on. Alright, out of the car.
Okay.
My King, are you okay?
(Secretly exerting force)
Open this door too.
Can we get out from this side?
Can we get out from this side later?
Yes.
(Struggling to get up)
The two of us can get out from here.
You have to close the door.
You have to be the last one
to close the door.
Yes.
Then just pull the electric handle
and leave.
Yeah.
So we don't even need
to use it to get in.
We can get in from that side.
Yes. We can get in from this side.
Ready?
A practice run, or go straight for it?
Come on.
Remember the order just now?
Let's just go for it.
(Warm-up time)
So nervous.
We got this!
Come on. Team cheer. Quick.
Come on.
Feels like we're about
to do something huge.
Come on. We've got this!
29 seconds, 29 and a half.
- 30 seconds. We've got this!
Come on.
Be careful not to twist your ankle.
One.
Two.
Three.
Go!
Three. Go!
(Timer running)
Go!
Hurry!
Come on! Get in!
(Lin Yi opens the car door quickly)
Get in!
(All car doors are open)
I'm crushed!
Get in!
Close the door!
(Closing doors takes time)
Okay.
Just wait.
Wait for the door.
Okay.
The moment it closes.
Open it!
Open the door!
(Honglei bolts out first)
Go!
Get in!
Thanks!
Come on! Hurry!
Get in!
Hurry!
Sit on my lap. Quick!
Get in!
Close the door!
Open the door!
- Open the door!
Wait a sec!
(The rear door is stuck on a post)
(Successfully opened)
Close the door!
Wait a sec!
Go!
Close it!
(Timer)
Okay.
(The timer hasn't stopped)
This door isn't closed.
This door isn't closed?
(Car door not closed?)
(Why?)
(When getting out)
(Door closing didn't trigger)
How many seconds?
47 seconds.
What should it have been?
30.
Such a big gap?
That's impossible.
There's no way to be faster than that,
I think.
Yeah, it really is tough.
Impossible.
(Can't believe it)
We were at full speed.
Absolutely impossible.
I have a sense of time in my head.
I think
even if the door wasn't closed properly,
we took 15 seconds max.
How could it be 40?
No.
When they tested this game,
there was a bug.
They thought
there wasn't much difference
between 35 and 30 seconds.
I feel like
time passed at different speeds.
That door was just too slow.
Yes.
There was something wrong with the door.
We'll give you 5 more seconds.
Okay.
You also get 35 seconds.
Now that's easier.
That's way too easy.
Come on. Get ready.
Let's hype ourselves up again.
One more time.
This time, it's 35 seconds.
For 35 seconds, we've got this.
Don't panic.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
- 35 seconds, we've got this!
One, two, three.
(Timer)
Go!
Get in!
Close it as soon as you're in!
Close it!
Close the door!
Close!
Back door.
Wait.
Open!
- Go!
This way, quick!
Go!
I'll go this way!
(No one closes the rear right door)
You go that way!
(Can they successfully close the door?)
(Successfully triggered)
Quick!
Come on!
Get in!
(Gong Jun opens the car door in advance)
Quick, get in!
Come on!
Slow down.
Come on.
Get in.
(Only Lin Yi left)
Come on. Hurry.
Quick!
Hurry!
Open!
(Timer)
Go!
- Go!
- Quick! Press it!
- Press it!
(Will they succeed this time?)
34 seconds.
Honglei!
We're awesome!
That was so cool.
We're very close to 30 seconds.
That's enough. Time to eat.
Everyone,
that was really cool.
Besides, we tricked you earlier.
Our fastest time was 40 seconds.
I knew it.
Come on. Let's give ourselves
a round of applause.
We're way too good.
We're so easy to fool.
Congrats, everyone.
You beat our test run by six seconds.
We beat your test run?
Aren't you amazing?
Nothing is impossible.
Come on. Let's set the bar
at 10 seconds.
Fixing that door issue
will speed things up.
It's just like
getting in like an action star.
Jumping in.
Just like an action star.
With your build,
you'd somehow squeeze through
and pop out over there.
Just hanging the two legs over.
Congrats, everyone,
on completing the challenge.
That felt great!
We won!
(Rotorua)
Next up, we'll have
a short experience.
You can choose
whether you want to experience
the volcanic mud coming your way.
A balloon filled with muddy water
will be suspended
above each member's head.
You need to lie underneath it,
holding the rope tied to the balloon.
By letting go of the rope,
you judge how close
the balloon gets to your face.
The closer it gets without popping,
the higher your score.
So we can only pull once
after letting go?
Yes.
We can't do it little by little?
Then what's the fun?
Come on. A little more.
Let go and grab.
Naiwen's good at this.
He's already got his glasses off.
Nai.
Here's the thing.
For our first round...
Master Guo.
The first round, we just
let go
and watch.
Come on, Fei. You've got this!
Three, two,
one, go!
Go!
That's tall enough to fit me.
Is that tall enough for Zhou Ye?
You used so much strength,
and it just stops here.
Look. Measure it.
Not even 1.45 meters.
Next.
Xingxu, you're up.
I...
I feel like
my eyes are...
Like a ruler.
Let me tell you.
Sometimes, when I see
Xingxu playing games,
I can't bear to watch.
There's always a feeling of sympathy.
Why?
I don't know.
You have this vibe
that makes people feel for you.
Yeah, a vibe that makes people
feel for you.
Come on.
Do your best.
Ready?
I'm ready.
One, two,
three!
An expert.
1.05 meters.
Wow!
This thing
is really hard to control.
Because once it drops,
it has
a gravitational acceleration.
It just goes, whoosh.
And even bounces a bit.
Fei, stop explaining.
Who's next?
Let me try.
Let me feel the weight.
Lie down and try it.
Trying it now doesn't...
(Piece of cake)
Expert.
Don't smirk.
I'm telling you.
I had the same reaction.
When it came down, I just
wasn't smirking anymore.
Got mud all over your face.
I'm going to wash my face.
She's over there playing with the water.
None of you even paid her attention,
you know?
(Nobody notices)
Monster.
Wen.
You look quite romantic this way.
If you get mud on your face
and then laugh...
Just keep your mouth shut for now.
Come on.
One, two, three!
That's so scary.
That's 1.3 meters, right?
1.3 meters.
About 1.3 meters.
Let's call it 1.3 meters.
Then I'm in second place for now.
Is it scary?
It's okay.
It's just that
this thing
will probably
mess with your judgment.
It's not this thing messing with you,
it's that
it has a drop-down effect.
So scary.
I'm too scared to play now.
Go, Nai.
(What must come will come)
No escaping it.
Nai, go by yourself first.
I'll go on my own first.
Go by yourself first.
Yeah, feel it yourself.
No.
Okay.
Close your mouth, Nai.
Nai is really scared.
Really nervous.
Ready!
Three, two, one!
Almost there.
Here, 85 centimeters.
Expert.
It's over. Naiwen's got this in the bag.
Come on.
Lin Yi, count it down.
Three, two,
one, go.
90.
Okay, done.
Nice.
Naiwen's first.
Jun's second.
Who's third?
Me.
After Xingxu, it's me.
(So I'm fifth)
After me, it's you last.
I don't think I can catch up
to the top three.
Here I come.
Three, two, one.
How much is this?
75.
Expert.
Very impressive.
I'm out of the top three.
Here.
Yuning, your turn.
I'm really scared of this kind of stuff.
Balloons popping, things like that.
That's great.
It's great that you're scared.
The thing I fear most
is a balloon popping. Come on.
(Testing it out)
Nice.
This is actually really easy.
This thing's actually very easy.
It's actually not that scary, right?
Come on.
(Official challenge)
Three, two, one.
1.1 meters.
Let me try again.
Try again.
Okay. Three, two, one.
One.
This hand,
I'm certain it's yours.
Yes.
This hand of yours is so brave.
No, just a little dirt on the shirt.
Just a little dirt on the shirt.
Alright. Anyone else want to challenge?
I'll go.
I must escape the third-to-last spot.
If you go,
and you win,
then I'll have to challenge.
You've got this.
Keep it up, Fei!
Come on. Three, two, one, go!
That's an improvement.
It's 1 meter now.
One more time.
Come on. Three, two, one, go!
I...
I didn't grab the rope.
It scared me!
How did it get to where you are?
No, I was playing over there.
And it just popped and scared me.
♪Turns out that meeting you♪
♪Is the joy hidden in the world♪
♪We still have to experience together♪
♪Exploring the novelty of the world♪
♪This is our wonderful encounter♪
♪I find good scenery
for you along the way♪
♪You are the joy hidden in the world♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪That day,
we traveled together far away♪
♪In countless late nights,
we exchanged courage♪
♪Our fates have already intertwined♪
♪In each other's life trajectories♪
♪We leave behind
bonds like no other for a lifetime♪
♪Turns out that meeting you♪
♪Is the joy hidden in the world♪
♪We still have to experience together♪
♪Exploring the novelty of the world♪
♪This is our wonderful encounter♪
♪I find good scenery
for you along the way♪
♪You are the joy hidden in the world♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪Traveling around the earth♪
♪Tasting all the freshness♪
♪Having traveled all corners♪
♪We still stand shoulder to shoulder♪
♪I'm glad to have met you♪
♪We sing beautifully together♪
♪Even if we're scattered in the future♪
♪Thankfully we still share the same sky♪